So this is the power the gods seek.
(ｼｬﾘｵｽ17世)
これが 神の求める力か｡
You have to save Mugaro!
(ｱｻﾞｾﾞﾙ)ムガロを…
俺たち魔族を助けてくれ！
You have to save the demons!
It's not working! I can't transform!
(ﾆｰﾅ･ﾄﾞﾗﾝｺﾞ)
ダメ 無理！ 変身できない！
両名を牢獄島において
無期の刑に処する｡
Imprison both in the prison tower,
where they will be held indefinitely.
みんなは あなたのこと➡
Everyone says you're a great king
who made the capital rich,
王都を繁栄させた
偉大な王様だって言うけど➡
but it's all a lie!
そんなのうそ！
あんたは ただの悪い王様だ！
You're just an evil king!
Well, well. If it isn't the great and noble knight,
gracing us with his presence.
(ﾌｧﾊﾞﾛ･ﾚｵｰﾈ)これは また
とんだ騎士様のご登場だ｡
Yo.
(ﾆｰﾅの声)
｢お母さん お元気ですか？➡
How are you, Mom?
I'm living with many friends now.
私は今 たくさんの仲間たちと
一緒に生活しています｡➡
王都と変わらず ここでも➡
Just like at the capital,
I've found work that is perfect for a girl like me.
女の子の私に
ぴったりの仕事をしています｣｡
あっ…｡
何やってる！
What are you doing?
(ｼﾞｬﾝﾇ)大丈夫…｡
あっ！
Are you okay?
おい 貴様 勝手な行動はするな！
You, stay out of this.
(ﾆｰﾅの声)
｢この場所は女性ばかりで➡
This place is full of women.
It's like our own little village.
まるで 里のようです｣｡
Start eating.
(看守)食事 始め！
(ﾆｰﾅの声)
｢不満があるとすると｣…｡
If I had to complain about something...
おかわり！
Seconds.
There isn't much to eat.
(ﾆｰﾅの声)｢ご飯が少ないのと｣…｡
(ﾆｰﾅの声)｢お日様の光を
見られないことです｣｡
And I don't get to see the sun.
≫ガシャン(扉の開閉音)
(ﾆｰﾅの声)｢でも➡
But I shouldn't act so spoiled.
わがままを言ってはいけません｡➡
Because I was given a special room
that's better than anyone else's.
私は特別に 誰よりも立派な部屋を
与えられているので➡
それだけでも感謝しています｣｡
So I'm thankful for that.
ガシャン
もう１０日目…｡
It's been ten days already.
あっ｡ 今日って 私の誕生日だ！
Today's my birthday.
Happy birthday to me...
Nina, age 17.
(ﾆｰﾅの声)｢ニーナ １７歳｡
私は 今日も元気です｣｡
I'm doing fine as always.
Rage of Bahamut
カン！ カン！
≫(ｶｲｻﾞﾙ)ファバロ
貴様 なぜ こんなとこにいる？
Favaro, what are you doing here?
いろいろあってな…｡
A lot happened.
What about you?
What did you do to end up here?
お前こそ 何やらかしたんだ？
女のケツでも触ったか？
(ｶｲｻﾞﾙ)ふざけたことを言うな！
Touch a woman's butt?
This is not a joke.
ん？
カン！ カン！ カン！
I have not committed any crimes.
私は 罪など犯していない｡
ただ アザゼルの反乱を
止めようとしただけだ｡
I only tried to stop Azazel's revolt.
Azazel did what?
アザゼルだ!?
静かにしろ｡
Be quiet.
あぁ… あいつ 王都にいんのかよ｡
王都に潜み➡
Is he in the capital?
He hid in the capital,
悪魔に非道な行いをする人間を➡
and murdered anybody
who treated demons inhumanely.
殺害し続けていた｡
ふん…｡ つぅことは➡
So they must have thrown you in here
because they thought you were with Azazel.
アザゼルの仲間とでも
勘違いされて➡
ここに ぶち込まれたのか｡
ふっ
相変わらず 要領の悪ぃ野郎だ｡
You're just as ham-fisted as ever.
(ｶｲｻﾞﾙ)アザゼルめ…｡
Azazel...
Why does he continue to act so recklessly?
なぜ あいつは
ああも無謀な行為を繰り返すのか｡
Even involving a young girl.
年端もゆかぬ少女まで
巻き込んで…｡
Girl?
少女？
ああ｡
Yes.
A girl named Nina who
wears clothes from a foreign land.
ニーナという
異国の服を着た少女だ｡
She was brought here to this prison with me.
私と一緒に
この牢獄へと連れてこられた｡
Nina? Nina...
ニーナ ニーナ…｡
それって
ちんちくりんの あのニーナか？
You mean that little shrimp Nina?
You know her?
知ってるのか？ お前｡
ああ まあ… ははっ｡
Well, you know...
俺に知らねぇ女は いねぇからよ｡
There's not a woman I don't know!
(回想)((おお～
飲んでくれ 飲んでくれ))
Drink up, drink up.
((どんどん飲んでくれ))
(女性)((すまないねぇ))
Drink up all you want.
Oh, thank you.
((なんの なんの｡ 賞金は
その日のうちに使いきるのが➡
It's nothing.
It's my policy to spend the bounty reward
before the day is out.
俺のポリシーだからよ))
((太っ腹だわ 若いのに))
How generous. And you're so young.
He's not that young.
((そんなに若くもないでしょ))
((いや～ 里の男たちは➡
Well, all the men leave the village for work,
so even he feels young.
みんな出稼ぎだから
こんなんでも新鮮だよ))
((うん))
((まったくだ))
Honestly, I've never seen hair like this before.
((こんな頭 初めて見た))
So, you mentioned a bounty reward, which means--
((そんで あんた
賞金ってことは…))
((ああ 賞金稼ぎだ))
Yeah, I'm a bounty hunter.
Favaro Leone, the bounty hunter.
((賞金稼ぎのファバロ･レオーネ))
((ああ～… 知らないね))
Never heard of you.
((おっかしいな｡
俺が倒した賞金首は➡
That's weird.
I mean, this was my 300th bounty
I've collected.
今回で もう３００人目だぜ？))
(女性)((３００人も？))
(女性)((あれまあ！))
Three hundred? Oh my.
((稼いだ賞金が
使いきれなくて困ってんだ))
I'm having real trouble
spending all the money I've earned.
Who have you taken down so far?
((今まで どんなの倒したの？))
((あんたみたいな➡
Real villains who would break the heart
of a good woman like you.
いい女を泣かせる悪党とか))
((よく言うよ))
Yeah, right.
What kind of cities have you been to?
((どんな街を
旅してきたんだい？))
Many with good women like you.
((あんたみたいな
いい女のいる街を次々と))
((何言ってんのよ あんた もう))
Oh, you're so full of it.
((ガタン ガタン！))
(一同)((ふふふふっ))
((あっ…))
Why are you so strong?
((なんつぅ力だ))
((そりゃあ 竜族だからね))
Well, we're dragonfolk, after all.
((あはははっ！))
((あっ ああ…))
((んんっ んんっ んっ… あっ…))
((ああっ！ なんだよ！ ん？))
What the hell?
Please make me your apprentice.
((弟子にしてください))
((はあ？))
I want to earn money.
((私 お金を稼ぎたいんです))
((賞金稼ぎじゃ稼げねぇよ))
((うそ！))
You can't earn anything as a bounty hunter.
Liar.
((最近は
悪党が減っちまったからな))
There aren't as many outlaws as there used to be.
You said you couldn't
spend all the money you've earned.
((稼いだ賞金が
使いきれないって言ってた))
((そんなこと言ったか？ 俺))
((言ってた！))
Did I say that?
You did. Please make me your apprentice.
((お願いです
弟子にしてください))
Give it up. A little shrimp like you isn't cut out for it.
((諦めな｡ お前みたいな
ちんちくりんには無理だ))
((賞金稼ぎは
力も強くないといけねぇし➡
Bounty hunters need to be strong
but also quick.
動きも速くないと…｡ ん？))
((力 強いです 私))
I am, you know. I'm pretty strong.
((ごほっ ごほっ
ごほっ ごほっ ごほっ…))
Please make me your apprentice.
Seriously?
((弟子にしてください！ あれ？))
((あんな化け物には
つきあいきれねぇ！))
Nope. I can't handle this freak show.
((はぁ はぁ はぁ…
おっ よっと))
Please, make me your apprentice.
((弟子にしてください))
((お前 竜族か？))
So you're dragonfolk.
((私のお母さんは人間です))
My mother is human.
My father is a dragon though.
((お父さんが竜だけど))
((ハーフかよ))
So you're half dragon?
((でも 力が強くて
足も速いでしょ？))
But I'm very strong and fast, right?
((ふふん))
((しょうがねぇな
この村にいる間だけだぞ))
Guess I don't have a choice.
Just while I'm here in the village.
((わあっ！))
((そのかわり 三食 宿付きだ))
But in exchange, I'll need a room
and three meals a day.
Yay!
((バン！ バン バン バン！))
((厄介なのに懐かれちまったな))
What a mess I've gotten myself into.
((あぁ～
さすが うわさの温泉だけあって➡
At least the hot springs are as relaxing as they say.
極楽だ))
It was worth coming all the way out here.
((わざわざ来た甲斐があったぜ))
((ぷはっ！ 気持ちいい～！))
That feels so good.
((お前 大胆なヤツだな))
((えっ？))
You're a bold one, aren't you?
((ああ～！ ああっ！))
Transforming into a dragon
when you see a handsome guy?
((いい男を見ると
竜になっちまうとは➡
お前も難儀なヤツだな))
That's some tricky stuff you have to deal with.
((つぅか なんで あんときだけ
竜になっちまったんだ？))
So how come you only transformed then?
((よく分かんないけど
アフロじゃなかったからかな))
I'm not exactly sure, but maybe it was
because you didn't have an afro.
((えっ？
これ イケてねぇのか？))
What? Is this not cool?
((そんなことより
今日の講義をお願いします))
Anyway, please, let's get to today's lesson.
Today's our last lesson.
((今日は最後の講義だ))
((えっ もう？))
What? Already?
Listen carefully, Nina.
((よく聞け ニーナ｡
挙げた首のことは➡
Quickly forgetting about the bounty you've caught
is the secret to being a good bounty hunter.
すぐ忘れることが
いい賞金稼ぎになる秘訣だ))
Why is that?
((なんでですか？))
((こっちが忘れちまえば➡
If we forget about it,
相手の恨みも飛んでこねぇ))
((へえ～ さすが師匠！))
then they won't harbor resentments either.
Wow, that's so deep, Master.
((奥が深いです｡
そんで？ そんで？))
So, what else?
((そんだけだ｡
お前に教えることは もうない))
That's all.
I've got nothing left to teach you now.
((腕を出せ))
Hold out your arm.
This is the mark of a bounty hunter.
((これが賞金稼ぎの証だ))
((わあ～！ おそろいだ！))
We match.
((ありがとうございます｡
ふふふっ))
Thank you very much.
((これで私も賞金稼ぎですね))
I guess now this makes me a bounty hunter too.
All right. I'm gonna do a great job.
((よっしゃ～！ 頑張るぞ！))
-Master, are you going on foot?
-Yeah.
((師匠 歩いて 行くんですか？))
((おう))
((お元気で 師匠！))
Take care!
I probably won't forget about you!
((私 師匠のこと
たぶん忘れない！))
((たぶんかよ…｡ あっ そうだ))
Probably?
Oh, that's right.
((仕事が欲しければ
アナティに行け))
Go to Anatae if you want work.
Once you get to the capital, go visit
the funny colored carriage.
((王都に行ったら
おかしな色した馬車を訪ねろ))
((そこで暮らしてる
アヒルと酔っ払いが➡
The duck and drunk that live there
are in charge of the bounty hunters.
賞金稼ぎの元締めだ))
((はい～！))
Okay.
((ニーナ
風は どっちに吹いてる？))
Nina, which way does the wind blow?
((こっち！))
((違う))
-This way.
-No, no.
It blows to tomorrow.
((なんか分かんないけど
明日で～す！))
I don't really get it, but to tomorrow!
Rage of Bahamut
I had no idea that girl was the red dragon.
あの少女が赤い竜だったとは…｡
んっ！ そうか アザゼルは
あの少女を利用して…｡
I see.
Azazel used the girl to...
無謀すぎるな｡
(ｶｲｻﾞﾙ)それで➡
Way too reckless.
So, what did you do to get put in here?
お前は 何をして入れられたのだ？
At the town I visited after the dragon village...
竜の里の次に立ち寄った街で➡
突然 王国の兵士１００人くらいに
囲まれてよぉ｡
I suddenly got surrounded
by about 100 royal soldiers.
俺も かなり奮闘したんだがな｡
I gave them a fight though.
((ぐぅ～ がぁ～…))
((ジョリ ジョリ ジョリ…
(髪を刈る音)))
((なんじゃ こりゃ～！))
What the hell is going on!
They took something precious from me.
俺は 大事なものを奪われ➡
I was subjected to one horrifying thing
after another.
恐ろしい目に次々と遭わせられた｡
I have to think the king was just toying with me.
ありゃあ
王様に遊ばれてたとしか思えねぇ｡
(ｶｲｻﾞﾙ)シャリオス王が？
まあ➡
By King Charioce?
I've just been held here ever since.
それからは ずっと
閉じ込められたままだけどな｡
Favaro...
ファバロ
お前を捕らえた兵士たちは➡
Were the soldiers who arrested you
漆黒の鎧を身に着けていたか？
wearing onyx black armor?
ああ 薄気味悪いヤツらだったぜ｡
Yeah, they were real creepy guys.
Wait, weren't you a captain?
そういえば
お前 団長だったんだろ？
Are your knights gonna be okay
団長が捕まっちまってて
お前の騎士団は大丈夫なのか？
after their captain got arrested?
Yes.
ああ｡ 私のせいで
惨めな思いをしていないといいが｡
I hope I haven't made them too miserable.
Wow, you're such a beast.
(女性)すご～い！ 魔獣みたい｡
(女性)かわいい！ 困ってる～｡
So cute! He's blushing.
脱いだら すごそう～｡
-You must look great under that shirt.
-You can show us tonight.
(ﾃﾞｨｱｽ)んん…｡
今晩 見せてくれてもいいんだぞ｡
(ﾃﾞｨｱｽ)
アレサンド そろそろ出よう｡
Alessand, we should leave soon.
-Where did Lady Jeanne go?
-Who's that?
ジｬンヌ様は どこに行ったんだよ｡
(女性)誰？ それ｡
Lady Jeanne D'Arc. My dream woman.
(ｱﾚｻﾝﾄﾞ)俺の憧れの
ジャンヌ･ダルク様だ！➡
俺は
ジャンヌ様がいるっていうから➡
I only joined the Orleans Knights
because Lady Jeanne was leading them.
オルレアン騎士団に
入ったのによぉ｡
≫(ｹﾙﾍﾞﾛｽ)お待たせしました～！➡
Sorry to keep you waiting.
It's Cerberus, the best guardian
to the gates of Hell.
地獄門ナンバー１門番の
ケルベロスで～す！➡
とっ…｡
(ｱﾚｻﾝﾄﾞ)ケル子～！
Cerby.
What's wrong, Al? You look all sad.
(ｹﾙﾍﾞﾛｽ)どしたの？ アレ君｡
しみったれた顔しちゃって｡
(ｱﾚｻﾝﾄﾞ)ケル子
俺 立派な騎士になれるかなぁ？
Cerby, you think I can
become a great knight one day?
ええ～
なれるんじゃない？ ｢そうだワン｣｡
I don't see why not.
Yeah.
そう…｡ いや 無理だよ｡
Really?
No, there's no way.
オルレアン騎士団は
もう終わりなんだ｡
The Orleans Knights are done for.
The captain got arrested.
団長が捕まっちまったし…｡
そっか 捕まっちゃったんだぁ｡
Oh, he got arrested?
おお～！ だったらさ いっそ
アレ君が団長になっちゃいなよ！
Oh, in that case...
Why don't you become the new captain, Al?
What? Me, the captain?
えっ？ お… 俺が団長？
Yeah. You're the captain now.
そうよ！ ｢あんたが団長｣！
You're the captain now.
(女性たち)あんたが団長！
(ｱﾚｻﾝﾄﾞ)俺が団長？
-I'm the captain?
-You're the captain.
(女性たち)あんたが団長！
(ｱﾚｻﾝﾄﾞ)俺が団長!?
-I'm the captain?
-You're the captain.
(女性たち)あんたが団長！
(ｱﾚｻﾝﾄﾞ)俺が団長～！➡
I'm the captain.
あはははっ！
(女性たち)かんぱ～い！
Yeah! Let's hear it for Al!
-I'm Alessand, captain of the Orleans Knights.
-You're the captain.
(ｱﾚｻﾝﾄﾞ)オルレアン騎士団団長の
アレサンドだぞ～｡
あっ｡
(ｼﾞｬﾝﾇ)食べるか？
-Do you want to eat this?
-Are you sure?
いいんですか？
(ｼﾞｬﾝﾇ)私は小食なんだ｡➡
I have a small appetite.
遠慮するな｡
ありがとうございます｡ ふふっ｡
I insist.
Thank you very much.
はむっ｡ ふふふっ｡
I'm Nina.
私 ニーナです｡
(ｼﾞｬﾝﾇ)私は ジャンヌ･ダルクだ｡
I am Jeanne D'Arc.
You're a good person, Ms. D'Arc.
ジャンヌ･ダルクさんは
いい人ですね｡
Jeanne is fine.
ジャンヌでいい｡
はい ジャンヌさん！
Okay, Ms. Jeanne.
Why were you brought to this prison?
(ｼﾞｬﾝﾇ)
そなたは なぜ この牢獄に？➡
You do not look like you would commit a crime.
犯罪を犯すようには見えないが｡
ジャンヌさんも見えませんよ｡
You don't either.
私のせいで 友達や知り合いが➡
Because of me, my friend
and an acquaintance were taken away.
いなくなってしまったんです｡
あっ…｡
I wasn't able to save them,
because I'm not experienced enough.
未熟だったから助けられなかった｡
(ｼﾞｬﾝﾇ)そうか｡
つらいことを聞いてすまなかった｡
I see.
I am sorry for bringing up a painful experience.
で そのあと ｱｻﾞｾﾞﾙっていう悪魔の
仲間だと思われちゃって➡
And after that,
they mistakenly thought I was working
with a demon named Azazel.
変な頭の団長さんと一緒に
ここに入れられちゃいました｡
So I was thrown in here with a captain,
one with funny hair.
あっ
どうしました？ ジャンヌさん｡
What's wrong, Jeanne?
Captain?
団長… それは
まさか カイザルのことか？
You do not mean Kaisar, do you?
へっ？
確か そんな名前だったかも…｡
I think that was his name.
I see.
≪そっか ジャンヌさん
みんなと知り合いだったんですね｡
You already knew everyone.
(ｼﾞｬﾝﾇ)もう何年も会っていないが｡
Although I have not seen them in years.
≪じゃあ ムガロちゃんは？
Then what about Mugaro?
She's a quiet girl with a mysterious power.
おとなしくて
不思議な力を持ってる女の子｡
左目がピカ～っつったら➡
When her left eye glows,
≪ぐわ～ってなるの｡
everything's like:
アザゼルが
奴隷市場で助けたんだって｡
Apparently Azazel saved her from a slave trader.
≪でも 私たちが捕まったとき➡
But when we were arrested,
≪光る人たちに
空の中へ連れていかれちゃった｡
Mugaro was taken up into the sky
by glowing people.
その子は 男の子ではなかったか？
Was the child not a boy?
女の子ですよ｡
No, she is a girl.
女の子ですよね？
She was a girl, right?
Could you tell me more about this child?
その子のことを
詳しく教えてくれないか？
The child still will not open up to us.
(ｿﾌｨｴﾙ)
いまだ 心を開こうとしません｡
It is likely he spent too much time in the lower world.
(ｶﾞﾌﾞﾘｴﾙ)
おそらく 下界にいた時間が➡
長すぎたのでしょう｡
(ｿﾌｨｴﾙ)いま少し お時間を｡
If you would allow me more time...
(ｶﾞﾌﾞﾘｴﾙ)
そんな時間はありません｡➡
There is no time we can spare.
あの子を神として覚醒させます｡
I will awaken the child into godhood.
(ｿﾌｨｴﾙ)早すぎませんか？
Do you not think it is too soon?
Regaining his true form...
(ｶﾞﾌﾞﾘｴﾙ)本来の姿を取り戻す…➡
That is something El should want as well.
それは エルにとっても
望ましいことなのです｡
Prepare the ritual at once.
(ｶﾞﾌﾞﾘｴﾙ)儀式の準備を急ぎなさい｡
(ｿﾌｨｴﾙ)
エル 私を覚えていないか？➡
El, do you not remember me?
I must apologize to you.
私は
お前に謝らなければならない｡➡
It is my fault that you were separated
from your mother.
お前たち親子が引き裂かれたのは
私のせいなのだ｡
I was once saved by your mother and your power.
私は以前 お前の母と
お前の力に命を救われたんだ｡
今度は私の番だ｡ 命に代えても
お前の母を助け出す｡
Now it is my turn.
I will save your mother, no matter the cost.
I ask that you do not forget that.
それを忘れないでくれ｡
(２人)んっ んんっ…｡
ほい！
Here.
ありがとう…｡
す… すごっ｡
Thank you.
Nina.
(ｼﾞｬﾝﾇ)ニーナ｡
ん？ どこだ…｡
Who said that?
あっ どうしました？
ジャンヌさん｡
Oh, what is it, Jeanne?
(ｼﾞｬﾝﾇ)手を止めずに聞いてくれ｡
Pretend to work as you listen.
私は ここから出る｡
I am going to leave this place.
そんなこと できるんですか？
Can you really do that?
I do not know.
分からない｡
But I wish to leave here and meet this child, Mugaro.
だが ここを出て
ムガロという子に会いたい｡
You want to meet Mugaro?
ムガロちゃんに？
I need to meet Mugaro and see something for myself.
会って確かめたいことがある｡➡
So please help me.
だから 協力してくれ｡
うん｡ ここから出て➡
Okay. Let's get out of here
and go see Mugaro together.
一緒に ムガロちゃんに
会いに行きましょう！
It's okay, it's okay
I cast the usual spell
Stagnation, stagnation
My words and heart are at odds
Default
I've taken all the paint
And mixed up all the colors
Until you're left with me
So fragile
Yet strong
Close to overflowing
But not spilling
Because I'm incomplete
I won't amount to much
This is just a good-luck charm
I'm not asking for your help
I was just clinging to you
Let's end it all today
I'm done living this pointless life
I've taken my last pointless breath
To whom it may concern
See you and goodbye
I killed the person I was yesterday
To whom it may concern
See you and goodbye
A new morning is coming
(ﾘﾀ)
じゃあ ヒッポグリフ またあとで｡
Okay, Hippogriff, I'll see you later.
These guys are such a handful.
まったく 世話が焼けるわね｡
-Ro-sham.
-Rock.
Hey.
-Rock, paper.
Ro-sham.
Next time on Rage of Bahamut: Virgin Soul,
"The Way She Was."
I've never heard of
a "to be continued" preview section before.
Me either.
Baha Soul!!
Baha Baha Baha Soul.
Tune in next time too, all right?
We'll watch too. Right, Alessand?